`- They know us in Paris.
[members speaking French]
We're a band named Cortis.
Please search it up.
[exciting music]
- [Woman] Come on in.
- Hey, "Vogue" this is -
- [All] Cortis.
- And we're here in Paris.
Two members are missing right now
and I think they will
join us like later on.
- So we're gonna order
some coffee and drinks.
- Yeah, we're in Paris,
so we need to drink some
cold coffee, I guess.
[upbeat music]
- [Barista] Really French is an espresso.
- Espresso?
- Espresso.
- Showy.
[laughs]
- That's...
- I've never tried it before,
but I'll get espresso.
- Yeah, I'll get it.
- Espresso?
- Yes. And also vanilla ice cream.
- [Barista] Okay.
- Yeah. Thank you. Thank
you. [speaks French].
- Oh, I'm nervous.
[laughs]
- After this, I definitely
need the ice cream.
- Yeah.
- Oh, whoa.
- It's very strong.
[laughs]
- Yeah. Very strong. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- James loves dessert.
Sometimes he doesn't like eat food.
I don't understand that,
but that's his style so.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Let me try it. Oh.
- It's melting. I prefer this way. Yeah.
- Yeah, we needed something sweet. Oh.
- Oh. Hey.
[members greeting each other in French]
- We're going to record shop in Paris.
- All right.
- Okay, okay.
[light music]
- Paris, yeah, it has its own vibe.
It has its own feeling to it
and I think it's a very inspiring city.
- This is my first time in Paris
and it's the group's first time
in Paris.
- Yes.
- First time in Europe, actually.
- The buildings, they're like beautiful.
- Everything's like beautiful.
- And like on the way I saw
like a couple just randomly sitting
in front of a building and
it just looked romantic.
It's just a vibe. It's true.
- Everything looks like
a scene in a movie.
- All right, guys, let's
go see this record store.
- There it is.
- Plastic Soul Records.
- Oh, Plastic Soul Records.
- Oh, they got the classics.
[upbeat music]
- We listen to every kinds
of, every kinds of music.
- As long as it's new to
us, it's a new experience,
we try to kind of accept it as it is.
[light music]
- I used to listen to Debussy in Korea.
To feel the vibe, I started
listening to Debussy again.
- This is my favorite
Rolling Stones album.
Stop playing with me.
"Exile on Main Street."
I've been listening to "Rocks Off."
This is a beautiful album.
- I want to try these two. Ralph Sutton.
Thank you so much.
[speaks French]
- "La Vie en rose."
This is one of the most
famous singers in France
and it was the 1962 first print.
- Celine Dion. CD is my
mother's spiritual mother
and she loves Celine Dion
and yeah, it passed on to me.
- So we got some good records
and we're moving on to the
acai shop to get some goodies.
- Acai in Paris.
- Let's go.
- Paris very different from Seoul.
- Yeah. I think Paris and Seoul,
they're both very big cities, I guess.
But I think Seoul is a bit...
- Bike, bikes!
- ...a bit more modern compared to Paris
and Paris is a bit more classic.
- Hello You. Hello.
- Hello me. Hello.
- Have a nice day.
- Have a good one.
- We're popping out in
Paris with acai bowls.
- The reason why we are eating
acai bowls, even in Paris,
because acai bowl is our favorite food.
- Paris is the city of love.
You gotta do what you love.
- When we were making the second album,
we were really into acai bowl,
like we had it almost
like every day a week.
- We noticed that the base gotta be good
to be a good acai.
- Yeah.
- Acai bowl.
- All the toppings,
they're just decorations.
- They're decorations.
- You gotta have a good base.
- After we noticed that,
we started to resonate with acai bowls.
It sounds weird, right?
But like we kind of wanted to
talk about it in our lyrics.
We wanna be the acai bowl,
the base itself, like something good.
Adventurous eater is probably James
because he just puts
me onto a lot of stuff.
Even this morning he was eating panini,
which I've never tried.
- Yes.
- And Keonho and Seonghyeon
will be the pickiest because...
- The youngest and pickiest.
- One French food I really want
to try, a very good Eclair.
- For me, like before we on stage,
I think I... I think I take a nap a lot.
After you take a nap, you can like feel
[speaks Korean]
- It feels like your brain was on restart.
- Yeah, restarts.
- No matter how much you're tired,
I think like as soon as
you go on the stage...
- You're forgetting that.
- My mode kind of change, you know?
- Meeting the fans,
getting engaged with them,
it's just always a different experience.
- Guys ready to go to the vintage store?
- Yeah, it's a good one. Let's go.
- [Woman] What words do
you know in French, guys?
- Nothing. I only know [speaks French]
[members speak French]
[woman speaks French]
- [Woman] That means I don't speak French.
[members speak French]
[jazzy music]
- I think like almost every clothes we buy
is vintage, I guess.
- When the clothes have stories to it
and then like certain designer
made it in certain year
and it becomes an archive piece.
- That's the reason why we go
crazy about vintage clothes,
like the history.
- Kurt Cobain once said this,
but it's like finding gems.
- I feel like vintage market
is like just getting bigger in Korea.
- Yes.
- But like in here, Paris, it's like
already all over the place, so...
[peaceful music]
- [Saleswoman] Can you
describe James's style?
- James? Oh.
- Rock band T-shirts.
- I think he custom make up...
- He crops. He crops his T-shirts.
- Distressed.
- Yeah, he cuts everywhere.
- Next victim.
- He has certain fits that he wear
and he got his own hairstyle going on.
- Hairstyle.
[members chuckle]
- Yeah, hairstyle is part
of fashion so like...
- I think I can copy it.
- Very edged.
- He always got the edgy hairline.
- I think he, he got this edgy.
- Yeah, he always got
like one part dangling.
Kind of pisses me off, but...
- Why?
- I don't know.
He always be just narrowing
that thing down, bro.
- I respect you.
That's your style. That's your style.
- I mess with you.
[light music]
- What piece would you choose, bro?
- Something like this.
[members laugh]
- Awesome.
- Yeah. Wanna wear it?
- Flamboyant. Balenciaga.
- Fab, fabulous.
- Orange one-piece.
- Actually, one-pieces
kind of look really comfy.
- It's gonna look great on you.
- Am I putting this on?
[members laugh]
- Okay. Next piece. Me?
Me for him.
- [Saleswoman] You look great.
- Why, why are you so worried?
- I'm nervous. I'm nervous.
- I'm not doing you like Juhoon did to me.
- Okay. Okay.
- Here you go.
[laughs]
- It's a swimsuit. Okay, cool.
- Swimsuit.
- So you swim.
- [All] Oh!
- I got you right there.
- Oh yes.
- You got a swimsuit. Gucci swimsuit.
- A swimmer.
- Yo, I got him so right.
- All right.
- All right, I think it's
time to hop on a cruise.
- Cruise.
- All right.
[light music]
- Gotta take them pics for the fans.
We in Paris!
[light music]
Feeling the air of Paris
is just the best part
of the trip, I guess.
- I'm looking forward to see
how much we're gonna take
inspiration and ideas
from like this trip here
and put it in our art.
[light music]
- They know us?
- Hello. Hi.
[members speak French]
- Yeah, they're saying Cortis.
[speaks French]
- Oh my God.
- Hey.
[speaks French]
- Yah, Cortis.
- Hey!
- I don't know. I don't
have any word of advice.
I don't want to say the
cliche be yourself thing.
It helps, but...
- I think you gotta find it yourself.
Advice doesn't work if you can't feel it.
- Exactly, right.
- In our generations, we kind
of lose track of dreaming
and just like sometimes
you think it's corny.
Sometimes you think it's just too cheesy,
but I think you really should.
You just should. You got to
live by something, you know?
[light music]
- [All] Bye, Vogue.
[group shouts in French]
- Yay!
- Yeah.
[group claps]
[light music]